A Guide to the Goochland County (Va.) Deed Books, 1737-1791
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Goochland County (Va.) Deed Books, 1737-1791
Library of Virginia
1146491-1146504
14 vols. (5984) photostatic pages
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Use microfilm copies, Goochland County, Reels 1-6.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in a transfer of court papers from Goochland County.
Historical Information
Goochland County was formed in 1728 from Henrico County.
Scope and Content
Deed books, 1737-1791, of Goochland County Court. The deed books record the name of the grantor and grantee, the residence of both individuals and the description of property being sold or transferred. The volumes have indexes which contains the first and last names of both parties. It is arranged alphabetically from A-Z.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Additional Goochland County Deed Books can be found on microfilm at The Library of Virginia. See A Guide to Virginia County and City Records on Microfilm
Access Terms
Goochland County (Va.). Circuit Court.; Goochland County (Va.)--History--18th century.; Deed books--Virginia--Goochland County.; Land records--Virginia--Goochland County.; Local government records--Virginia--Goochland County.
Contents List
- Deed book, No. 3 1737-1742, 1146491
- Deed Book, No. 4 1741-1745, 1146492
- Deed Book, No. 5 1745-1749, 1146493
- Deed Book, No. 6 1748-1755, 1146494
- Deed Book, No. 7 1755-1759, 1146495
- Deed Book, No. 8 1759-1765, 1146496
- Deed Book, No. 9 1765-1769, 1146497
- Deed Book, No. 10 1769-1775, 1146498
- Deed Book, No. 11 1775-1777, 1146499
- Deed Book, No. 12 1777-1779, 1146500
- Deed Book, No. 13 1779-1784, 1146501
- Deed Book, No. 14 1784-1788, 1146502
- Deed Book, No. 15, Pt. 1 1788-1791, 1146503
- Deed Book, No. 15, Pt. 2 1788-1791, 1146504